

# **AKSHAY KUMAR THAYATH**

Senior Travel consultant

Professional Travel consultant with over 05 years of experience . Seeking a challenging career in a reputed organization, where i can fully utilize my abilities and work experience to produce high standard of work and to strengthen my inherent capabilities. Specialized in reservation and ticketing for both retail and corporate clients. Take every chance to familiarize myself with what goes on in the tourism industry.

akshaykumart619@gmail.com



+971562157004



Dubai, United Arab Emirates

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Senior Travel Consultant DeiraTravels & Tourist Agency

11/2017 - Present

Dubai, Uae

Tasks & Responsibilities

- Cooperating with clients to determine their needs and advising them appropriate destination, modes of transportation, travel dates, costs and accommodations Issued personal business and corporate bookings.
- Use promotional techniques and prepare promotional materials to sell itinerary tour packages
- Provide the highest standard of customer service to all clients and attend all queries in a timely and appropriate manner. Available for them 24/7 if there is any emergency.
- Ensure the ticket booking, follow the correct date and time limit for frequent clients especially for Corprate passengers. nform customers about the mandatory requirements for their
- Organizing travel arrangements from beginning to end, including tickets, accommodation and transportation for domestic and International trips based on the clients/companies needs, budgets and expectations.
- Provided Tour packages ,Hotel booking and Visa services

## Reservation Excecutive Star of Asia Tours & Travel

01/2014 - 10/2017

Kerala, India

Tasks & Responsibilities

- Issued tickets both International and Domestic
- Arranged Inbound tours and accommodations
- Dealt with occurring travel problems and complaints

## **CORPORATE COMPANIES HANDLED**

Faisal Al Nusif Trading Co Llc

Emirates Technical Service Llc (Bukhatir Group)

Terna Sa Abu dhabi

Omani Food Stuff Trading

Reem Contracting Llc

Sho Cho Facilities Management Services Llc

#### **SKILLS**

Experienced working under pressurized fast paced

Good communication and Interpersonal skills

Strong Knowledge in reservation system -Galileo

Having strong problem solving skills

Actively listen and Quick response

#### PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATES

IATA/UFTAA Foundation Diploma (03/2014 - 03/2015)

Al Hind Aviation Academy, Kannur, India

#### **EDUCATION**

BA (Sociology) Perusing

Higher Secondary (05/2012)

#### GDS KNOWN

**GALILEO.AMADEUS & SABRE** 

#### **LANGUAGES**

English

Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

Malayalam

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Professional Working Proficiency

#### **INTERESTS**

Travelling

Swimming

Football